selectbutton.com 2016-06-24

# Privacy Policy - SelectButton

If you continue to browse and use this website, you are agreeing to comply with and be bound by the following terms and conditions of use, which together with our privacy policy govern SelectButton's relationship with you in relation to this website. If you disagree with any part of these terms and conditions, please do not use our website.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at press@selectbutton.com.

If you are a publisher or developer that is interested in having your product featured on SelectButton. Please send an email to press@selectbutton.com.

At SelectButton, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.selectbutton.com and how it is used.

#### User-Provided Information

You provide us information about yourself, such as your name and e-mail address, when you register with us. Also, you may provide information when you participate in sweepstakes and contests, message boards and chat rooms, and other interactive areas of our Website. If you correspond with us by email, we may retain the content of your email messages, your email address and our responses.

#### Cookies Information

When you visit the Website, we may send one or more cookies – a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters – to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser and lets us help you log in faster and enhance your navigation through SelectButton. A cookie does not collect personal information about you. We use both session cookies and persistent cookies. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Website. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser’s directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the Service may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled.

#### Log Files

Log file information is automatically reported by your browser each time you access a web page. When you register with or view our Website, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends whenever you visit any website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, referring / exit pages and URLs, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed, and other such information.

#### Clear Gifs Information

When you use the Service, we may employ clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons) which are used to track the online usage patterns of our users anonymously. No personally identifiable information is collected using these clear gifs. In addition, we may also use clear gifs in HTML-based emails sent to our users to track which emails are opened by recipients. The information is used to enable more accurate reporting, improve the effectiveness of our marketing, and make us better for our users.

#### New Technology

As we adopt additional technology, we may also gather information through other means and there may be other technologies present that act in a similar way but are protected by confidentiality.

#### Third Parties

We expect our partners, advertisers and affiliates to respect the privacy of our users. Be aware, however, that third parties, including our partners, advertisers, affiliates and other content providers accessible through our Website, may have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices.

You should also be aware that if you voluntarily disclose personally identifiable information on message boards or in chat areas, that information can be viewed publicly and can be collected and used by third parties without our knowledge and may result in unsolicited messages from other individuals or third parties. Such activities are beyond our control and outside the scope of this document.

#### Links to Other Websites

We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Website nor the information or content contained therein. Please remember that when you use a link to go from our Website to another website, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. User browsing and interaction on any other website, including those that have a link on our Website, is subject to that other website’s own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding.

#### Third Party Advertisements and Technologies

We use third-party advertising companies to serve advertisements when you visit our Website. In the course of advertisements being served to you, a unique third-party cookie or other advertising technology may be placed on your browser. This advertising technology uses information derived from your visits to the Website to target advertising within this Website. This information is used for many purposes, for example, it helps us try to ensure that you do not see the same advertisements over and over again. We also use this information to help select and display targeted advertisements that we believe may be of interest to you (sometimes called “online behavioral advertising” or “interest-based advertising” or “OBA”). We also use web beacons, provided by third-party advertising companies, to help manage and optimize our online advertising. Web beacons enable us to recognize a browser’s cookie when a browser visits this Website, to learn which banner ads bring users to our Website and to deliver more relevant advertising.

In addition, our advertisers or other third parties may use other third-party advertising technology to target advertising on the Website and other websites. We do not control the data collection and use practices of these other third parties. You should read the privacy notices of the websites you visit in order to determine what companies may be collecting information on those websites.

#### Changes to Our Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to change this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of our Website following the posting of changes to these terms will constitute acceptance of those changes. Information collected prior to the time any change is posted will be used according to the rules and law that applied at the time the information was collected.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Website, or your dealings with this Website, please contact us at press@selectbutton.com.
